Inventory of the Nell Eurich papers 1922-2000
Hoover Institution Archives
- The Learning Industry and Adult Learning Project file
  - Education
    - Colleges and universities
      - Fielding Institute, California, 1987 (Box-folder 15: 7)
      - Five Colleges, Inc., Massachusetts, 1984 (Box-folder 15: 8)
      - Marymount College, New York, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 15: 9)
      - Michigan State University, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 15: 10)
      - New Jersey Institute of Technology, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 15: 11)
      - New School for Social Research, New York, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 15: 12)
      - New York University, 1988 (Box-folder 16: 1)
      - New York University, Gallatin Division, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 16: 2)
      - Queens College, North Carolina, 1988 (Box-folder 16: 3)
      - School of New Learning, Illinois, 1989 (Box-folder 16: 4)
      - Thomas A. Edison State College, New Jersey, undated (Box-folder 16: 5)
      - UCLA extension, California, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 16: 6-7)
      - University of Kansas, undated (Box-folder 16: 8)
      - University of the State of New York (Regents Degree), 1981, undated (Box-folder 16: 9)
      - Walden University, Institute for Advanced Studies, Florida, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 16: 10)
      - Wentworth Institute of Technology, Massachusetts, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 16: 11)
      - Western Kentucky University, 1986 (Box-folder 16: 12)
    - Programs
      - Technical workers
        - Health care workers program, University of Alabama, Birmingham, 1987-1989, undated (Box-folder 17: 1)
      - Managers
        - General, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 17: 2)
        - Articles, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 17: 3)
        - Research study and brochure, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 17: 4)
        - American Assembly of Collegiate Schools of Business project, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 17: 5)
        - Schools for managers
          - Columbia and New York University, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 17: 6)
          - University of Arkansas, 1988 (Box-folder 17: 7)
          - Other schools, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 17: 8)
- Professional positions and activities file
  - Marshall Scholarships, Middle States Committee, 1967-1917 (Box-folder 17: 9)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 17: 10)
  - American Association of Colleges, history, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 17: 11)
  - Aspen Public High School, Colorado
    - Forum on power, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 18: 1)
  - New College
    - New College publications, including catalogs, 1993-1994, undated (Box-folder 18: 2)
    - Money Guide, 1994, 1996 (Box-folder 18: 3)
    - 1997
      - Correspondence, meeting minutes, and general documents, 1997 (Box-folder 18: 4)
      - Auditor's report, 1997 (Box-folder 18: 5)
    - 1996
      - Correspondence, meeting minutes, and general documents, 1996 (Box-folder 18: 6)
      - Auditor's report, 1996 (Box-folder 18: 7)
    - 1995
      - Correspondence, meeting minutes, and general documents, 1995 (Box-folder 19: 1-2)
      - College classification, 1995 (Box-folder 19: 3)
    - 1994
      - Correspondence, meeting minutes, and general documents, 1994 (Box-folder 19: 4-5)
      - Auditor's report, 1994 (Box-folder 19: 6)
      - Fundraising, 1994 (Box-folder 19: 7)
    - Correspondence, meeting minutes, and general documents, 1993 (Box-folder 19: 8)
    - Correspondence and general documents, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 20: 1)
    - Fall meeting, 1992 (Box-folder 20: 2)
- The Learning Industry and Adult Learning Project file
  - Post-publication material
    - Vendors
      - National Technology University
        - General, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 20: 3)
        - Annual report, 1995 (Box-folder 20: 4)
        - Annual reports, brochures, and other printed matter, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 20: 5)
        - NTUplink newsletters, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 20: 6)
  - Research files for The Learning Industry
    - Statistics
      - Statistics from Corporate Classrooms file, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 20: 7)
      - Adult education, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 20: 8)
      - Job training, 1986 (Box-folder 20: 9)
    - Bibliographies
      - Bibliography of Howard Bowen works, 1987 (Box-folder 20: 10)
      - Bibliography and reviews of Eli Ginzberg works, 1987 (Box-folder 20: 11)
      - Bibliographies from UNESCO, ERIC, and the University of Minnesota, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 21: 1)
      - General bibliographies, 1987 (Box-folder 21: 2)
    - Lists of research materials and resource directory, 1987, undated (Box-folder 21: 3)
      Contains list of materials for chapter 2
    - General material, articles, and research studies
      - General, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 21: 4)
        Includes background information on Adult Learning Project
      - General, 1986 (Box-folder 21: 5)
      - Study outlines, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 21: 6)
      - Articles, 1976-1988, undated (Box-folder 22: 1-3)
      - Articles and clippings bibliography, undated (Box-folder 22: 4)
      - Research studies, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 22: 5)
      - Research studies, size and scope statements, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 22: 6)
    - Other literature
      - American Society for Training and Development (ASTD), 1981-1988 (Box-folder 22: 7)
      - Correspondence of Robert L. Craig, American Society for Training and Development (ASTD), 1981-1986 (Box-folder 22: 8)
      - National Center for Research in Vocational Education, 1988 (Box-folder 22: 9)
      - National Institute for Work and Learning, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 23: 1)
      - Roosevelt Center, High-Flex Society, 1987 (Box-folder 23: 2)
      - United States Congress hearings by Joint Economic Committee, 1987 (Box-folder 23: 3)
  - Education
    - Community colleges
      - Schools
        Includes college brochures, pamphlets, course schedules, statistics, annual reports, and correspondence
        - Cedar Valley College, 1986, undated (Box-folder 23: 4)
        - Central Community College, Nebraska, 1986, undated (Box-folder 23: 5)
        - City Colleges of Chicago, Illinois, 1988 (Box-folder 23: 6)
        - Clark Technical College, Ohio, 1986 (Box-folder 23: 7)
        - Community College of Allegheny County, Pennsylvania, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 23: 8)
        - Columbus State Community College, 1987 (Box-folder 23: 9)
        - Dawson Community College, Montana, 1986, undated (Box-folder 23: 10)
        - District One Technical Institute, Wisconsin, 1986 (Box-folder 23: 11)
        - Emanuel County Junior College, Georgia, 1986 (Box-folder 23: 12)
        - Garden City Community College, Kansas, 1986 (Box-folder 23: 13)
        - Guilford Technical Community College, North Carolina, 1985-1986, undated (Box-folder 23: 14)
        - Hartford State Technical College, Connecticut, 1987 (Box-folder 23: 15)
        - Houston Community College System, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 23: 16)
        - John Woods Community College, Illinois, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 24: 1)
        - Johnson County Community College, Kansas, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 24: 2)
        - LaGuardia Community College, New York, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 24: 3)
        - Lord Fairfax Community College, Virginia, 1986-1987, undated (Box-folder 24: 4)
        - Los Angeles Community College District, California, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 24: 5)
        - Maricopa Community Colleges, Arizona, 1986-1988, undated (Box-folder 24: 6)
        - Massachusetts Bay Community College, 1986 (Box-folder 24: 7)
        - Miami-Dade Community College, Florida, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 24: 8)
        - Newbury College, Massachusetts, undated (Box-folder 25: 1)
        - New York City Technical College/CUNY, New York, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 25: 2)
        - Niagara County Community College, New York, 1986 (Box-folder 25: 3)
        - Parkland Community College, Illinois, 1986 (Box-folder 25: 4)
        - Paul Smith's College, New York, 1987 (Box-folder 25: 5)
        - Piedmont Virginia Community College, Virginia, 1987 (Box-folder 25: 6)
        - Rancho Santiago Community College District, California, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 25: 7)
        - Saddleback College, California, 1986 (Box-folder 25: 8)
        - Umpqua Community College, Oregon, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 25: 9)
        - Valencia Community College, 1988, undated (Box-folder 25: 10)
        - West Virginia State College, West Virginia, 1986 (Box-folder 25: 11)
        - Yakima Valley College, Washington, 1986, undated (Box-folder 25: 12)
        - Other schools, 1986 (Box-folder 25: 13)
      - Programs
        - Technical workers
          - Article on community colleges, technical training, and economic development, 1988 (Box-folder 25: 14)
          - Programs, 1986-1987, undated (Box-folder 25: 15)
        - Missing persons
          - General, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 25: 16)
      - Distance education and delivery systems
        - American Association of Community and Junior Colleges (AACJC)
          - Survey of telecourse use, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 26: 1)
          - Instructional Telecommunications Consortium, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 26: 2)
          - ACCESS (information sharing network), 1987 (Box-folder 26: 3)
          - Community College Satellite Network, circa 1988 (Box-folder 26: 4)
        - Other programs
          - Bergen Community College, Eastern Educational Consortium, New Jersey, 1985 (Box-folder 26: 5)
          - Central Piedmont Community College, North Carolina, 1987 (Box-folder 26: 6)
          - Dallas Telecourses, Texas, 1987 (Box-folder 26: 7)
          - Intermountain Community Learning and Information Services, Utah, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 26: 8)
          - Other community college programs, 1987 (Box-folder 26: 9)
  - Education
    Includes materials on telecourses
  - Prisons
    - Addresses of state program directors, 1986 (Box-folder 26: 10)
    - Clippings, correspondence, and notes, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 26: 11)
    - Research studies
      - General, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 26: 12)
      - Report by Sarah White, 1988 (Box-folder 26: 13)
      - Federal Bureau of Prisons, undated (Box-folder 26: 14)
    - Programs (Box-folder 26-27)
      - Florida Department of Corrections, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 26: 15)
      - New York Department of Correctional Services, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 27: 1)
      - Windham School District, Texas, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 27: 2)
      - Other programs, 1987 (Box-folder 27: 3)
  - State and local
    - Programs
      - Managers
        - Research studies, New York, government employee education and training, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 27: 4)
        - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching (CFAT) Study of Higher Education in Arkansas, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 27: 5)
      - Missing persons
        - Correspondence, notes, and clippings, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 27: 6)
        - Research studies, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 27: 7-8)
      - Programs by state
        Includes memoranda, reports, and other materials discussing literacy, the Job Training Partnership Act (JTPA), and workfare
        - California
          - General, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 28: 1)
          - Employee training panel, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 28: 2)
          - Workfare, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 28: 3)
        - Florida, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 28: 4)
        - Illinois, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 28: 5)
        - Illinois, Private Industry Council of Chicago, Job Training Partnership Act (JTPA), 1986-1987 (Box-folder 28: 6)
        - Indiana, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 28: 7)
        - Kentucky, 1988 (Box-folder 28: 8)
        - Massachusetts, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 29: 1)
        - Massachusetts, Executive Office of Labor, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 29: 2)
        - Michigan, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 29: 3)
        - New York
          - Statistics and memoranda on meetings, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 29: 4)
          - Research studies, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 29: 5)
          - Printed matter, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 29: 6)
          - Benchmark: A Bimonthly Report on Occupational and Continuing Education in New York State, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 29: 7)
          - Adult literacy programs, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 30: 1)
          - Job Training Partnership Act (JTPA), 1985-1987 (Box-folder 30: 2)
          - Workfare, 1987 (Box-folder 30: 3)
        - Pennsylvania, 1986 (Box-folder 30: 4)
        - South Carolina
          - Articles, 1988 (Box-folder 30: 5)
          - Report by Felisa Tibbitts and notes, 1988 (Box-folder 30: 6)
          - Commission on Higher Education report, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 30: 7)
          - "Year of the Reader" conference material, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 31: 1)
        - Other states
          - General, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 31: 2)
          - "Jobs for the Future" reports, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 31: 3)
          - Welfare reform, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 31: 4)
    - Distance education and delivery systems
      - Clippings, reports, and lists, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 31: 5)
      - Programs by state
        - Kentucky, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 31: 6)
        - Maine, 1987 (Box-folder 31: 7)
        - North Carolina, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 31: 8)
        - South Carolina, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 31: 9)
        - West Virginia, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 31: 10)
        - Other programs, 1987, undated (Box-folder 31: 11)
  - Corporations
    - Correspondence, memoranda, and notes, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 31: 12)
    - Articles, 1981-1989 (Box-folder 32: 1-3)
    - Articles on size and scope of corporate training, 1986 (Box-folder 32: 4)
    - Research studies (Binder 32)
      - General, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 32: 5-6)
      - "Analyzing Corporate Collegiate Partnerships" by Lee Teitel, 1987 (Box-folder 32: 7)
- Education, training, and technology file
  - Adult learning and higher education
    - Coeducation
      - General, 1966-1977 (Box-folder 33: 1)
      - Reports on coeducation, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 33: 2)
        Includes reports on preparatory schools
      - Newhall College of Cambridge University, 1966, undated (Box-folder 33: 3)
        Includes photographs of campus
    - Innovative education
      - Articles, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 33: 4)
      - Research papers, 1967-1977 (Box-folder 33: 5)
        Includes paper by Alvin Eurich
      - Printed matter related to education, 1963-1982 (Box-folder 33: 6-7)
      - Printed matter related to education, 1963-1972 (Box-folder 34: 1-2)
      - Open universities, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 34: 3)
      - "External Degrees and Noncampus Study" by Barry Schwenkmeyer, 1973 (Box-folder 34: 4)
      - Papers by William Arrowsmith, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 34: 5)
      - Proposal by Jose Ortega y Gasset and letter, 1949, 1974 (Box-folder 34: 6)
      - Proposals for education in the mid-Hudson region, 1965-1967, undated (Box-folder 34: 7)
      - Experimental and new programs
        - Clippings related to education reform and experimental institutions, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 34: 8)
        - Institutional publications, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 35: 1)
        - Correspondence and papers on institutional publications, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 35: 2)
        - Bradford College, 1982, undated (Box-folder 35: 3)
        - Dynamy Institute, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 35: 4)
          Includes conference materials
        - Eckerd College, 1976 (Box-folder 35: 5)
          Includes consulting work of Eurich
        - Wesleyan University, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 35: 6)
    - American Association of Community and Junior Colleges (AACJC), 1989-1990 (Box-folder 35: 7)
    - American Council on Education
      - General, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 36: 1)
      - Higher Education & National Affairs newsletters, 1988 (Box-folder 36: 2)
      - Clippings and correspondence on "Memorandum to the 41st President,", 1988 (Box-folder 36: 3)
      - Coalition of Adult Education Organizers, 1988 (Box-folder 36: 4)
      - Program on Noncollegiate Sponsored Instruction (PONSI), 1980-1988 (Box-folder 36: 5)
- The Learning Industry and Adult Learning Project file
  - Corporations
    - Printed matter and correspondence, 1981-1988 (Box-folder 36: 6)
    - American Society for Training and Development (ASTD), 1987, undated (Box-folder 36: 7)
    - Alden Seminar white paper, undated (Box-folder 36: 8)
    - Corporate colleges
      - Lists of corporate colleges and contacts, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 36: 9)
        Includes clippings and correspondence
      - Corporate annual reports, A to I, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 36: 10)
      - Corporate annual reports, J-W, 1987 (Box-folder 37: 1)
      - Aetna Institute, 1987 (Box-folder 37: 2)
      - American Institute of Banking, New York, 1986 (Box-folder 37: 3)
      - Ameritech, 1988 (Box-folder 37: 4)
      - AT&T, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 37: 5)
      - Bell South, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 37: 6)
      - Chrysler Institute, Learning and Training Center, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 37: 7)
      - DeVry Institute of Technology (company of Bell and Howell), 1985, undated (Box-folder 37: 8)
      - Digital Equipment Corporation
        - General, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 38: 1)
        - Letters to Gael Dussault, 1991 (Box-folder 38: 2)
        - Notes on videotape, 1990 (Box-folder 38: 3)
        - Artificial intelligence fellowship program, 1989, undated (Box-folder 38: 4)
        - Information on audiocassette program, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 38: 5)
        - Computer conferencing, 1989 (Box-folder 38: 6)
        - Secretarial training, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 38: 7)
        - Decworld '90 conference, 1990 (Box-folder 38: 8)
      - Dupont Continuing Education, 1986 (Box-folder 38: 9)
      - General Electric, 1982 (Box-folder 38: 10)
      - General Motors Institute, 1983 (Box-folder 38: 11)
      - Hamburger University, McDonald's, 1986 (Box-folder 38: 12)
      - Hewlett-Packard, 1982-1986, undated (Box-folder 38: 13)
      - International Business Machines (IBM)
        - Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 38: 14)
        - Clippings, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 38: 15)
        - Other literature, undated (Box-folder 38: 16)
      - Manufacturers Hanover, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 38: 17)
      - Nippon Steel Human Resources Development Co., 1987-1993 (Box-folder 38: 18)
      - Northrop University, 1982 (Box-folder 38: 19)
      - Philadelphia College of Textile and Sciences, 1988 (Box-folder 38: 20)
      - Polaroid, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 39: 1)
      - Procter & Gamble, 1986 (Box-folder 39: 2)
      - Rand Corporation, 1982-1992 (Box-folder 39: 3)
      - Squibb College, 1989 (Box-folder 39: 4)
      - Tokyo Electric Power: TEPCO Educational Institute, 1987 (Box-folder 39: 5)
      - Toyota Technological Institute, 1987 (Box-folder 39: 6)
      - Westinghouse, undated (Box-folder 39: 7)
        Includes floppy disk
      - Worthington Industries, 1987 (Box-folder 39: 8)
    - Programs
      - Technical workers
        - AT&T, 1987 (Box-folder 39: 9)
        - Cincinnati Milacron, 1986 (Box-folder 39: 10)
        - International Business Machines (IBM), 1985 (Box-folder 39: 11)
        - Motorola, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 39: 12)
        - Xerox Learning Centers, undated (Box-folder 39: 13)
        - Other programs, 1987 (Box-folder 39: 14)
  - Research files for The Learning Industry
    - Background issues
      - Changing nature of work
        - Articles, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 39: 15)
        - Special sections of newspapers, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 39: 16)
        - Other literature, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 40: 1)
      - Competitiveness and productivity
        - Articles, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 40: 2-3)
        - Other literature
          - General, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 40: 4)
          - National Center on Education and Employment, 1987 (Box-folder 40: 5)
      - Job market reports and predictions
        - Articles, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 41: 1)
        - Other literature, 1986 (Box-folder 41: 2)
      - Job training
        - Memoranda, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 41: 3)
        - Articles, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 41: 4)
        - Other literature, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 41: 5)
      - Education and older people
        - Articles, 1981-1989 (Box-folder 41: 6)
        - Report by Lydia Bronte, 1987 (Box-folder 41: 7)
        - Organizations
          - American Association of Retired Persons (AARP), 1986-1988 (Box-folder 41: 8)
          - Elderhostel, 1988, undated (Box-folder 41: 9)
          - Travelers Older American Program, 1985-1986, undated (Box-folder 41: 10)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Notes, 1988 (Box-folder 41: 11)
        - Printed matter, 1983-1989 (Box-folder 41: 12)
    - Target groups
      - Trade and technical workers
        - Correspondence, memoranda, and notes, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 42: 1)
        - Articles, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 42: 2)
        - Research studies
          - General, 1986 (Box-folder 42: 3)
          - Agency for International Development, Latin American and Caribbean Bureau (AID/LAC) report on training needs in Latin America, undated (Box-folder 42: 4)
          - Report by Sarah White, 1988 (Box-folder 42: 5)
        - Other literature, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 42: 6)
        - American Society for Training and Development (ASTD) conference material, 1987 (Box-folder 42: 7)
        - Occupations
          - Communications
            - General, 1987-1988, undated (Box-folder 42: 8)
            - Staff report, 1985 (Box-folder 42: 9)
          - Construction
            - Trade programs, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 42: 10)
            - National Association of Home Builders, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 42: 11)
          - Health care, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 42: 12)
  - Unions
    - Programs
      - Technical workers
        - Apprenticeships
          - General, 1988, undated (Box-folder 43: 1)
          - Research studies and other literature, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 43: 2)
          - Materials of Ed Czarnecki, 1979-1988 (Box-folder 43: 3)
          - Materials of Kenneth Edwards
            - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers apprenticeship standards, 1971-1987 (Box-folder 43: 4)
            - "The Perspective of Organized Labor on Improving America's Productivity,", 1983 (Box-folder 43: 5)
            - Comments on draft report on apprentice training, 1988 (Box-folder 43: 6)
            - Binder of selected items on worker training, 1922-1987 (Box-folder 43: 7)
              Includes photocopies
          - United States Department of Labor, 1977-1988 (Box-folder 43: 8)
          - Communications Workers of America, 1987, undated (Box-folder 44: 1)
          - Seafarers International Union, Harry Lundeberg School, 1986 (Box-folder 44: 2)
          - United Auto Workers, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 44: 3)
      - Managers
        - Directories, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 44: 4)
        - Articles and other literature, 1988, undated (Box-folder 44: 5)
        - Research study on education opportunities for labor, 1968, 1986 (Box-folder 44: 6)
        - George Meany Center for Labor Studies, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 44: 7)
      - Missing persons
        - General, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 44: 8)
        - Articles and research studies, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 44: 9)
        - Other literature, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 44: 10)
        - Materials of Kenneth Edwards, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 45: 1)
        - Job Training Update newsletters and HRDI Advisory newsletters, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 45: 2)
        - AFL-CIO conference, 1986 (Box-folder 45: 3)
    - Distance education and delivery systems, 1987 (Box-folder 45: 4)
  - Nonprofit organizations
    - Programs
      - General
        - Cambridge Center for Adult Education, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 45: 5)
        - New York Botanical Garden, 1988 (Box-folder 45: 6)
        - Sherman Adult Education, 1986 (Box-folder 45: 7)
      - Missing persons
        - Articles, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 45: 8)
        - Research studies, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 45: 9)
  - Research files for The Learning Industry
    - Target groups
      - Professionals
        - Occupations
          - Physicians
            - General, 1975-1988 (Box-folder 46: 1)
            - Articles, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 46: 2)
            - Other literature
              - General, 1982-1988 (Box-folder 46: 3)